- IF YOU ASK ME,
I THINK THE GIRL'S IN LOVE.
- [WOMAN] THAT'S WHAT IT
IS, I THINK HE'S GOT--
- [MAN] AW, MAN, SEE,
NOW YOU GUYS ARE ALL
YOU'RE ALL GETTING CARRIED AWAY.
LOOK WHO IT IS.
- WHAT'S UP WITH YOU GUYS?
Y'ALL JUST STARING?
- YOU ALL, I HAVE AN
ANNOUNCEMENT TO MAKE.
WE HAVE SOMEONE VERY SPECIAL.
(LAUGHTER)
- COME ON, JANET, SERIOUSLY,
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- JUST GETTING IN
FOLKS' BUSINESS.
Y'ALL SO NOSEY.
- NAH, DUDE, FOR
REAL, WHAT'S UP?
- YEAH.
- OK, YOU GUYS
REALLY WANT TO KNOW?
- YEAH, I DO.
I REALLY WANNA KNOW.
- I DON'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS.
Y'ALL JUST NEVER GIVE UP.
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
♪ SHOT ♪
♪ LIKE AN ARROW
THROUGH MY HEART ♪
♪ THAT'S THE PAIN I FEEL ♪
♪ I FEEL WHENEVER WE'RE APART ♪
♪ NOT TO SAY THAT I'M
IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ BUT WHO'S TO SAY
THAT I'M NOT? ♪
♪ I JUST KNOW THAT
IT FEELS WRONG ♪
♪ WHEN I'M AWAY TOO LONG ♪
♪ IT MAKES MY BODY HOT ♪
♪ SO LET ME TELL YOU, BABY ♪
♪ I'LL TELL YOUR MAMA ♪
♪ I'LL TELL YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ I'LL TELL ANYONE WHOSE
HEART CAN COMPREHEND ♪
♪ SEND IT IN A LETTER, BABY ♪
♪ TELL YOU ON THE PHONE ♪
♪ I'M NOT THE KIND OF GIRL
WHO LIKES TO BE ALONE ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ M-I-S-S YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH, BABY ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ M-I-S-S YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I'M RUSHING HOME JUST
AS SOON AS I CAN ♪
♪ I'M RUSHING HOME TO
SEE YOUR SMILING FACE ♪
♪ AND FEEL YOUR WARM EMBRACE ♪
♪ IT MAKES ME FEEL SO GOOD ♪
♪ SO I'LL TELL YOU BABY ♪
♪ I'LL TELL YOUR MAMA ♪
♪ I'LL TELL YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ I'LL TELL ANYONE WHOSE
HEART CAN COMPREHEND ♪
♪ SEND IT IN A LETTER, BABY ♪
♪ TELL YOU ON THE PHONE ♪
♪ I'M NOT THE KIND OF GIRL
WHO LIKES TO BE ALONE ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ M-I-S-S YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ BABY ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ M-I-S-S YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ M-I-S-S YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ BABY ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ M-I-S-S YOU MUCH ♪
♪ MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I BROUGHT YOU HERE ♪
♪ TO TELL THE WORLD ♪
♪ I MISS YOU ♪
♪ I'LL TELL YOUR MAMA ♪
♪ I'LL TELL YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ I'LL TELL ANYONE WHOSE
HEART CAN COMPREHEND ♪
♪ SEND IT IN A LETTER ♪
♪ TELL YOU ON THE PHONE ♪
♪ I'M NOT THE KIND OF GIRL
WHO LIKES TO BE ALONE ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ I MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ BABY ♪
♪ I REALLY MISS YOU MUCH ♪
♪ M-I-S-S YOU MUCH ♪
- [JANET JACKSON]
THAT'S THE END?